var questionArray = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
    selection: ["JavaScript is a light weight, interpreted programming language.",
                "JavaScript is designed for creating network-centric applications.",
                "JavaScript is complementary to and integrated with Java.",
                "All of the above."],
    answer: "All of the above.",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about callbacks?",
    selection: ["A callback is a plain JavaScript function passed to some method as an argument or option.", 
                "Some callbacks are just events, called to give the user a chance to react when a certain state is triggered.", 
                "Both of the above.", 
                "None of the above."],
    answer: "Both of the above.",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
    selection: ["toExponential()", 
                "toFixed()", 
                "toPrecision()", 
                "toLocaleString()"],
    answer: "toFixed()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
    selection: ["charAt()", 
                "charCodeAt()", 
                "concat()", 
                "indexOf()"],
    answer: "charCodeAt()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating whether a reference string comes before or after or is the same as the given string in sort order?",
    selection: ["localeCompare()", 
                "search()", 
                "substr()", 
                "concat()"],
    answer: "localeCompare()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following function of String object returns a string representing the specified object?",
    selection: ["toLocaleUpperCase()", 
                "toUpperCase()", 
                "toString()", 
                "substring()"],
    answer: "toString()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed in the specified size as if it were in a <font size = 'size'> tag?",
    selection: ["fixed()", 
                "fontcolor()", 
                "fontsize()", 
                "bold()"],
    answer: "fontsize()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following function of Array object removes the last element from an array and returns that element?",
    selection: ["pop()", 
                "push()", 
                "join()", 
                "map()"],
    answer: "pop()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following function of Array object removes the first element from an array and returns that element?",
    selection: ["reverse()", 
                "shift()", 
                "slice()", 
                "some()"],
    answer: "shift()",
  },
  {
    question: "JavaScript makes my brain hurt",
    selection: ["Yes", 
                "Absolutely", 
                "All of the above", 
                "None of the above"],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
];